

# Nina Zanarelli

# **Professional Summary**

Creative Designer with 2 years of experience working in the UI and Service Design field. Achievments include winning the McGinnis Competition award of March 2021 and the Social Venture Plan Competition award on April 2021. Original and clever with the ability to lead large design and development teams.

# **Work History**

## The Student Community - Chief Designer

Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania 03/2020 - Current

- Obtained approval of concepts by submitting rough drafts to management or to client.
- Developed design deliverables that elevated, differentiated and functioned on-brand and on-strategy.

## LookUp - LookUp Social Innovator

United States

12/2020 - 06/2021

One of 40 youth leaders awarded the LookUp StartUp Social Innovation Grant in 2021 for designing a ground-breaking solution to digital wellbeing and humane technology. Winners of this highly selective national competition join the Leadership Lab, a virtual experimential platform from which young leaders emerge with the knowledge and skills to lead and affect social change. Working with a highly-respected executive mentor, Social Innovators transform their ideas into action in order to address market forces and shift social norms to a healthier more humane digital world.

#### Politecnico di Milano - Salone del Mobile Volunteer

Milan, Italy

04/2019 - 05/2019

Volunteer at Salone del Mobile Fair, one of the most well known fair in the design field. I set up and attended the stand of Politecnico of Milan located at the fair. I also worked on other temporary exhibitions in the city of Milan during the period of the fair.

#### **V&A Dundee - International Workshop**

Dundee, Scotland

02/2019 - 02/2019

I attended an international workshop in Scotland with other students from 12 different countries. During the workshop we collaborated with the V&A Dundee museum to improve the customer service and make the experience at the museum more enjoyable.

nina.zanarelli@gmail.com

+393483615850

Milan, Italy 20147

## **Portfolio**

• https://nina.zanarelli.github.io/

#### Skills

- Adobe Creative Suite
- Creative design layouts
- Customized template design
- Illustration
- Teamwork skills
- Project presentations

## **Education**

Expected in 09/2022

Politecnico di Milano

Milan, Italy

Master of Arts: Product Service System Design

07/2020

Politecnico di Milano

Milan, Italy

Bachelor of Arts: Interior Design

07/2017

Scientific High School - Vittorio Veneto

Milan, Italy

High School Diploma